Register of the Jacques Leprette papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Conferences, Seminars, and Official Visits File, 1975-2003
  - Future Role of the United Nations in an Interdependent World roundtable, United Nations Institute for Training and Research, Moscow, USSR, 1988 September 5-9
    - Conference papers (Box-folder 126: 8-10)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 126: 11)
    - Report (Box-folder 126: 12)
  - Les enjeux de la francophonie conference, Institut de Langue et de Culture FranÇaises, Lyon, France, 1988 October 20 (Box-folder 126: 13)
  - Séminaire sur la présidence de la Communauté Économique Européenne, Madrid, Spain, 1988 November 2-3
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 126: 14)
    - List of participants and program (Box-folder 126: 15)
  - Négociations multilatérales politiques seminar, Institut International d'Administration Publique, Paris, France, 1989 January 30 - February 3 (Box-folder 126: 16)
  - Présentation de l'administration franÇ;aise, Institut International d'Administration Publique, Paris, France, 1989 March 6-17 (Box-folder 126: 17)
  - Paix et sécurité internationale: mythe et réalité conference, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 1989 March 20-22
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 126: 18)
    - Notes (Box-folder 129: 19)
    - Paper (Box-folder 129: 20)
    - Programs (Box-folder 126: 21)
  - Fortieth anniversary of the Council of Europe, Strasbourg, France, 1989 May 5 (Box-folder 126: 22)
  - Troisième Conférence des chefs d'état et de gouvernement des pays ayant en commun l'usage du français, Dakar, Senegal, 1989 May 24-26
    - Clippings (Box-folder 127: 1)
    - Compilation of documents (Box-folder 127: 2)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 127: 3)
    - Programs (Box-folder 127: 4-5)
    - Reports (Box-folder 127: 6)
    - Resolution (Box-folder 127: 7)
    - Statistics (Box-folder 127: 8)
    - Text of play performed in conjunction with conference (Box-folder 127: 9)
    - Post-conference committee meetings file (Box-folder 127: 10)
      Serial issues, speech, and reports
      - 1990 (Box-folder 127: 10)
      - 1991 (Box-folder 127: 11)
  - Défense nationale et sécurité colloquium, Institut du Droit de la Paix and du Developpement, Université de Nice, France, 1989 June 15-16 (Box-folder 128: 1)
    Correspondence, list of participants, and program
  - Espace juridique francophone et droits de l'homme conference, Université de Limoges, France, 1989 October 2-3 (Box-folder 128: 2)
    Correspondence, notes, and program
  - La pratique française dans le domaine de la protection internationale des droits de l'homme colloquium, Centre de Droit International de Nanterre, France, 1989 October 12-13 (Box-folder 128: 3)
  - Négociations multilatérales politiques seminar, Institut International d'Administration Publique, Paris, France, 1990 January 15-18 (Box-folder 128: 4)
  - L'Économie et la paix conference, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 1990 March 1-3
    - Correspondence, list of participants, and program (Box-folder 128: 5)
    - Notes (Box-folder 128: 6)
  - De Gaulle en son siècle conference, Institut Charles de Gaulle, Paris, France, 1990 November 19-24
    - Brochures (Box-folder 128: 7)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 128: 8)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 128: 9)
    - Directory (Box-folder 128: 10)
    - Lists of participants (Box-folder 128: 11)
    - Notes (Box-folder 128: 12)
    - Papers and presentations (Box-folder 128: 13)
    - Programs (Box-folder 128: 14)
  - Paix et sécurité internationale dans un monde multipolaire conference, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 1991 February 28 - March 2
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 128: 15)
    - Notes (Box-folder 128: 16)
    - List of participants and programs (Box-folder 128: 17)
  - De Gaulle et les États-Unis d'Amérique debate, Asssociation France États-Unis, Grenoble, France, 1991 April 4 (Box-folder 129: 1)
  - Conference on the United Nations, Académie du Royaume du Maroc, Casablanca, Morocco, 1991 April 22-24
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 129: 2)
    - Papers (Box-folder 129: 3)
    - Program (Box-folder 129: 4)
  - L'Afrique dans le monde: la négociation seminar, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 1991 September 30 - October 4 (Box-folder 129: 5)
    Correspondence, notes, and programs
  - Quatrième Conférence des chefs d'état et de gouvernement des pays ayant en commun l'usage du français, Paris, France, 1991 November 19-21
    - Correspondence and information dossier (Box-folder 129: 6)
    - Report (Box-folder 129: 7)
    - Serial issues (Box-folder 129: 8)
    - Transcript of proceedings (Box-folder 129: 9)
  - Négociations multilatérales politiques seminar, Institut International d'Administration Publique, Paris, France, 1992 January 15-17 (Box-folder 129: 10)
  - Les données nouvelles de la sécurité en Europe: l'impact de la réunification allemande conference, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 1992 February 27-29
    - Correspondence and notes (Box-folder 129: 11)
    - List of participants and programs (Box-folder 129: 12)
    - Papers and speeches (Box-folder 130: 1)
  - La francophonie dans la communauté scientifique mondiale: la responsabilité partagée des politiques et des scientifiques conference, Haut Conseil de la Francophonie, Paris, France, 1992 March 31 - April 2
    - Correspondence and press release (Box-folder 130: 2)
    - Transcript of proceedings (Box-folder 130: 3)
  - Visit of French officials to Egypt, 1992 April 21-24
    - Brochures (Box-folder 130: 4)
    - Itinerary and contact information (Box-folder 130: 5)
    - Memoranda and reports (Box-folder 130: 6-7)
    - Program (Box-folder 130: 8)
  - Est-Ouest: regards croisés et coopération en Europe au XXe siècle colloquium, Université du Maine, Le Mans, France, 1992 December 9-10 (Box-folder 130: 9)
  - L'ONU et les organisations régionales: quelle coopération face au défi de la sécurité internationale? conference, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 1993 March 4-6
    - Correspondence, list of participants, programs, and report (Box-folder 130: 10)
    - Notes (Box-folder 130: 11)
    - Papers and speeches (Box-folder 130: 12)
  - Quel nouvel ordre mondial? Mythes et realités conference, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 1994 March 3-5
    - Clipping and correspondence (Box-folder 131: 1)
    - List of participants and programs (Box-folder 131: 2)
    - Notes (Box-folder 131: 3)
    - Papers and speeches (Box-folder 131: 4)
  - ONU mécanique workshop, Biblothèque Publique d'Information, Paris, France, 1995 February-September (Box-folder 131: 5)
    Program
  - Prévention et résolution pacifique des conflits internationaux seminar, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 1995 March 12-19 (Box-folder 130: 6)
  - Entre guerre et paix: demain l'O.N.U.? conference, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 1995 March 16-18
    - Correspondence, list of participants, notes, and program (Box-folder 131: 7)
    - Papers and speeches (Box-folder 131: 8)
  - Les interventions militaires de l'O.N.U.: 1990/1995, roundtable discussion, Centre de droit international et européen, Université de Versailles, Saint-Quentin-en-Yvelines, France, 1995 April 12
    - Clippings (Box-folder 131: 9)
    - Correspondence, program, and questionnaires (Box-folder 131: 10)
  - Fiftieth anniversary of the United Nations commemoration, New York City, 1995 April 25 (Box-folder 131: 11)
  - Pratique diplomatique et négociation internationale seminar, Institut International d'Administration Publique, Paris, France, 1995 May 2 - June 2 (Box-folder 131: 12)
  - Présentation du Conseil de Sécurité et du principe des négociations multilatérales seminar, Institut Européen des Hautes Études Internationales, Nice, France, 1995 May 23-24 (Box-folder 131: 13)
    Correspondence, course materials, and program
  - Fiftieth anniversary of l'École Nationale d'Administration, Paris, France, 1995 September 30
    - Brochure and program (Box-folder 131: 14)
    - Clippings (Box-folder 131: 15)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 131: 16)
  - Pratique diplomatique et négociations internationale seminar, Institut International d'Administration Publique, Paris, France, 1995 October 23 - November 24 (Box-folder 131: 17)
  - Cycle de formation de diplomates tunisiens seminar, Institut International d'Administration Publique, Paris, France, 1995 October 30 - November 24 (Box-folder 131: 18)
  - La France et l'O.T.A.N.: 1949-1996 colloquium, Centre d'Études d'Histoire de la Défense, Paris, France, 1996 February 8-10 (Box-folder 131: 19)
    Correspondence
  - L'invention de la diplomatie, roundtable discussion, École Pratique des Hautes Études, Paris, France, 1996 February 9 (Box-folder 131: 20)
    Abstracts and program
  - Comment va la paix? conference, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 1996 April 18-20
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 132: 1)
    - List of participants, program, and summary (Box-folder 132: 2)
    - Notes (Box-folder 132: 3)
  - Fifteenth Regional Conference of European United Nations Associations, Luxembourg, 1996 August 26-28 (Box-folder 132: 4)
    Correspondence, paper, and program
  - Pratique diplomatique et négociations internationales seminar, Institut International d'Administration Publique, Paris, France, 1996 October 7 - November 8 (Box-folder 132: 5)
  - L'O.T.A.N. dans le système international de sécurité conference, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 1997 March 13-15
    - Correspondence, list of participants, and programs (Box-folder 132: 6)
    - Papers and speeches (Box-folder 132: 7)
    - Transcript of proceedings (Box-folder 132: 8)
  - Semaine internationale de la francophonie, Québec, 1997 March 16-22
    - Clipping, map, press release, reports, and serial issues (Box-folder 132: 9)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 132: 10)
    - Program (Box-folder 132: 11)
    - Notes (Box-folder 132: 12)
    - Speech (Box-folder 132: 13)
  - Les négociations internationales seminar, Institut Européen des Hautes Études Internationales, Nice, France, 1997 May 5-7 (Box-folder 132: 14)
    Correspondence, course materials, program
  - Visit of Lucien Bouchard, Paris, France, 1997 September 28 - October 2
    - Clippings (Box-folder 132: 15)
    - Serial issues (Box-folder 132: 16)
  - Cinquième Conférence des chefs d'état et de gouvernement des pays ayant en commun l'usage du français, Hanoi, Vietnam, 1997 November 14-17
    - Clippings (Box-folder 132: 17)
    - Serial issues (Box-folder 132: 18)
  - La coopération multilatérale peut-elle garantir les équilibres internationaux? seminar, 1997 November 24 - December 19 (Box-folder 132: 19)
  - L'Union Européenne en l'an 2000 colloquium, Institut FranÇais de Relations Internationales, Paris, France, 1997 December 12-13 (Box-folder 132: 20)
  - Négociations multilatérales politiques seminar, Institut International d'Administration Publique, Paris, France, 1997 December 15-19 (Box-folder 132: 21)
  - Mondialisation et sécurité internationale conference, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 1998 March 19-21
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 133: 1)
    - List of participants, program, and summary (Box-folder 133: 2)
    - Papers and speeches (Box-folder 133: 3)
  - Regards croisés sur l'Europe réunifiée colloquium, Institut Français des Relations Internationales, Paris, France, 1998 December 14-15 (Box-folder 133: 4)
    Notes and program
  - Crises et sécurité internationale conference, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 1999 March 4-6 (Box-folder 133: 5)
    Papers and speeches
  - La négociation internationale seminar, Institut International d'Administration Publique, Paris, France, 1999 March 15 - April 9 (Box-folder 133: 6)
  - Fiftieth anniversary of the Council of Europe commemoration, Strasbourg, France, 1999 May 5
    - Correspondence and speech (Box-folder 133: 7)
    - Press review (Box-folder 133: 8-10)
    - Program (Box-folder 133: 11)
  - La fonction diplomatique seminar, Institut International d'Administration Publique, Paris, France, 1999 October 11 - November 5 (Box-folder 133: 12)
  - L'entrée dans le XXIe siècle: les enjeux de la mondialisation conference, Institut français des relations internationales, Paris, France, 1999 November 3-4 (Box-folder 133: 13)
    Programs
  - Charles de Gaulle: la Jeunesse et la Guerre 1890-1920 colloquium, Fondation Charles de Gaulle, Lille, France, 1999 November 5-6 (Box-folder 133: 14)
  - Vers un nouvel ordre international: les réponses de l'Europe colloquium, Fondation Singer-Polignac, Paris, France, 1999 December 15 (Box-folder 134: 1)
  - Le r#x00F4;le des élites d'Europe centrale et orientale dans la fin de la Guerre froide et dans la redéfinition du monde conference, Institut français des relations internationales, Paris, France, 1999 December 17 (Box-folder 134: 2)
    Brochures and program
  - Interventions humanitaires et sécurité internationale conference, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 2000 March 9-11
    - Correspondence, list of participants, and program (Box-folder 134: 3)
    - Papers and speeches (Box-folder 134: 4)
  - Gouvernance et sécurité internationale conference, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 2001 March 29-31
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 134: 5)
    - List of participants, program, and summary (Box-folder 134: 6)
    - Papers and speeches (Box-folder 134: 7)
    - Transcript of proceedings (Box-folder 134: 8)
  - Énergies et climats conference, Académie des Sciences, Paris, France, 2001 April 23
    - Clippings (Box-folder 134: 9)
    - Correspondence and program (Box-folder 134: 10)
    - Memoranda and reports (Box-folder 134: 11-12)
  - La «Communauté internationale»: concept, bilan, perspectives colloquium, Fondation Singer-Polignac, Paris, France, 2001 November 14
    - Clippings (Box-folder 134: 13)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 134: 14)
    - Papers (Box-folder 134: 15)
    - Program (Box-folder 134: 16)
  - Le monde après le 11 septembre: quels enseignements? conference, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 2002 March 7-9
    - Background article and brochure (Box-folder 135: 1)
    - Correspondence and notes (Box-folder 135: 2)
    - List of participants and programs (Box-folder 135: 3)
    - Paper (Box-folder 135: 4)
    - Transcript of proceedings (Box-folder 135: 5)
  - De l'exégèse du Nouveau Testament à l'engagement œcuménique conference, Universität Basel, Basel, Switzerland, 2002 May 3-4
    - Correspondence and program (Box-folder 135: 6)
    - Notes (Box-folder 135: 7)
    - Papers (Box-folder 135: 8)
  - Les États-Unis et l'Europe élargie dans le système international de sécurité conference, Académie de la Paix, Monte Carlo, Monaco, 2003 March 13-15
    - Background articles (Box-folder 135: 9)
    - Correspondence (Box-folder 135: 10)
    - List of participants and programs (Box-folder 135: 11)
    - Notes (Box-folder 135: 12)
    - Papers and speeches (Box-folder 135: 13)
    - Transcript of proceedings (Box-folder 135: 14)
- Organizations File, 1953-2003
  Clippings, correspondence, notes, printed matter, speeches, and other materials, arranged alphabetically by name of organization and by physical form thereunder
  - Académie de la Paix et de la Sécurité Internationale
    - Correspondence
      - 1997 (Box-folder 135: 15-16)
      - 1998 (Box-folder 135: 17)
      - 1999 (Box-folder 136: 1)
      - 2000 (Box-folder 136: 2)
      - 2001-2003 (Box-folder 136: 3)
    - Directory, 1998 (Box-folder 136: 4)
    - Notes, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 136: 5)
    - Printed matter
      - Brochures, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 136: 6-7)
      - Clippings, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 136: 8)
  - Académie des Sciences Morales et Politiques, Institut de France
    - Correspondence
      - 1998 (Box-folder 136: 9)
      - 1999 (Box-folder 136: 10)
      - 2000 (Box-folder 136: 11)
      - 2001 (Box-folder 137: 1-2)
      - 2002 (Box-folder 137: 3)
    - Election ceremony file
      Materials relating to the ceremony in honor of Jacques Leprette's election to the academy and his receiving a sword (l'épée d'académicien) on that occasion
      - Account of ceremony by Jacques Leprette, 2000 (Box-folder 137: 4)
      - Biographical data, undated (Box-folder 137: 5)
      - Clippings, 2000 (Box-folder 137: 6)
      - Commemorative booklet, 2000
        - Proofs (Box-folder 137: 7-8)
        - Printed copy (Box-folder 137: 9)
        - Mailing list (Box-folder 137: 10)
      - Correspondence
        - General
          - 1999-2000 (Box-folder 137: 11)
          - 2000 (Box-folder 138: 1)
        - Responses to invitations, 2000 (Box-folder 138: 2-10)
        - Responses to invitations, 2000 (Box-folder 139: 1-2)
      - Designs for sword, 2000 (Box-folder 139: 3)
      - Financial records, 2000 (Box-folder 139: 4)
      - Lists of invitees, 2000 (Box-folder 139: 5-10)
      - Lists of invitees, 2000 (Box-folder 140: 1)
      - Lists of subscribers to sword fund, 2000 (Box-folder 140: 2-3)
      - Program, 2000 (Box-folder 140: 4)
      - Scrapbook, 2000 (Box-folder 140: 5)
      - Speech by Jean Cluzel, 2000 (Box-folder 140: 6)
    - History of academy compiled by Eric de Lussy, 2000 (Box-folder 140: 7-8)
    - Meetings file
      Agendas, notes, speeches, and transcripts of proceedings
      - 1997-1998 (Box-folder 141: 1)
      - 2000 (Box-folder 141: 2)
      - 2001 (Box-folder 141: 3-4)
      - 2002 (Box-folder 141: 5-6)
      - 2003 (Box-folder 141: 7)
    - Notebooks, 2000 (Box-folder 141: 8-9)
    - Printed matter
      - Brochures and bulletins, 1996-2002 (Box-folder 142: 1-2)
      - Clippings, 1995-2002 (Box-folder 142: 3)
    - Speech by Jacques Leprette, "Notice sur la vie et les travaux d'Oscar Cullman (1902-1999),", 2001 April 24
      - Lists of invitees, 2001 (Box-folder 142: 4-5)
      - Clippings, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 142: 6)
      - Correspondence
        - 2001 (Box-folder 142: 7-9)
        - 2002 (Box-folder 142: 10)
      - Dossier on Oscar Cullman, 1962-2001 (Box-folder 142: 11)
        Clippings, correspondence, monograph excerpts, and notes
      - Dossier on Oscar Cullman, 1962-2001 (Box-folder 143: 1-2)
      - Notes, 2001 (Box-folder 143: 3-4)
      - Holograph drafts, 2001 (Box-folder 143: 5-8)
      - Typescript drafts, 2001 (Box-folder 143: 9-12)
      - Typescript drafts, 2001 (Box-folder 144: 1-17)
      - Printed copy, 2001 (Box-folder 144: 18)
    - Working group on the French press
      - Correspondence and background articles
        - 2000 (Box-folder 145: 1-2)
        - 2002-2003 (Box-folder 145: 3)
      - Reports
        - 2000 (Box-folder 145: 4)
        - 2001 (Box-folder 145: 5-7)
        - 2002 (Box-folder 145: 8-9)
        - 2003 (Box-folder 145: 10)
  - Agence France-Presse
    - Correspondence, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 146: 1)
    - Meetings file, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 146: 2)
      Correspondence, notes, and transcripts of proceedings
  - Association Albert Plécy
    - Brochures, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 146: 3)
    - Correspondence, 1987-2003 (Box-folder 146: 4)
    - Meetings file
      Agendas, correspondence, notes, reports, and transcripts of proceedings
      - 1987-1989 (Box-folder 146: 5)
      - 1990 (Box-folder 146: 6)
      - 1991 (Box-folder 146: 7)
      - 1993 (Box-folder 146: 8)
      - 1994 (Box-folder 146: 9)
    - Postcards, undated (Box-folder 146: 10)
    - Press dossiers
      - 1987-1992 (Box-folder 146: 11)
      - 1998-2002 (Box-folder 146: 12)
  - Association des Anciens Élèves-Officiers de Cherchell-Mediouna
    - Correspondence
      - 1992-1993 (Box-folder 146: 13)
      - 1994 (Box-folder 146: 14)
      - 1995 (Box-folder 146: 15)
      - 1996-2003 (Box-folder 146: 16)
    - Meetings file, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 146: 17)
      Agendas, correspondence, and transcripts of proceedings
    - Printed matter
      - Brochures, 1994 (Box-folder 146: 18)
      - Clippings, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 147: 1)
      - Newsletters, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 147: 2)
      - Serial issue, 1993 (Box-folder 147: 3)
  - Association Nationale pour les Stages à l'Étranger (ANSE)
    - Clippings, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 147: 4)
    - Correspondence
      - 1990-1992 (Box-folder 147: 5)
      - 1993 (Box-folder 147: 6)
      - 1994 (Box-folder 147: 7)
      - 1995 (Box-folder 147: 8)
      - 1996 (Box-folder 147: 9)
      - 1997 (Box-folder 147: 10)
    - Meetings file
      - 1993-1994 (Box-folder 147: 11)
      - 1995 (Box-folder 147: 12)
      - 1996 (Box-folder 147: 13)
    - Reports
      - 1993 (Box-folder 147: 14)
      - 1994 (Box-folder 147: 15)
      - 1995 (Box-folder 147: 16)
      - 1997 (Box-folder 147: 17)
  - Centre de Conférences Internationales de Paris
    - Brochure, 1992 (Box-folder 147: 18)
    - Correspondence and report, 1990-1994 (Box-folder 147: 19)
  - Centre d'Information Civique
    - Bulletin and study, 1995 (Box-folder 148: 1)
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box-folder 148: 2)
  - Centre Médico-Chirurgical de Bligny
    - Brochures, 1953-1974 (Box-folder 148: 3)
    - Correspondence
      - 1986-1988 (Box-folder 148: 4)
      - 1989-1991 (Box-folder 148: 5)
    - Meetings file
      - 1986 (Box-folder 148: 6)
      - 1987
        - January-June (Box-folder 148: 7)
        - July-December (Box-folder 148: 8)
      - 1988
        - January-June (Box-folder 148: 9)
        - July-December (Box-folder 148: 10)
      - 1989
        - January-June (Box-folder 148: 11)
        - July-December (Box-folder 148: 12)
      - 1990
        - January-June (Box-folder 148: 13)
        - July-December (Box-folder 148: 14)
      - 1991
        - January-June (Box-folder 149: 1)
        - July-December (Box-folder 149: 2)
    - Report, 1987 (Box-folder 149: 3)
    - Statutes, 1970 (Box-folder 149: 4)
  - Échanges et Consultations Techniques Internationaux (ECTI)
    - Correspondence, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 149: 5)
    - Meetings file
      - 1995-1997 (Box-folder 149: 6)
      - 1998-2001 (Box-folder 149: 7)
    - Reports, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 149: 8)
  - École Spéciale Militaire de Saint-Cyr
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 149: 9)
    - Meetings file, 1988 (Box-folder 149: 10-12)
      Agendas, correspondence, notes, reports, and transcript of proceedings
    - Student records, 1988 (Box-folder 149: 13-15)
    - Student records, 1988 (Box-folder 150: 1-5)
  - Fondation Carnegie, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 150: 6)
    Correspondence and reports
  - Fondation et Institut Charles de Gaulle
    - Correspondence
      - 1987-1989 (Box-folder 150: 7)
      - 1990-2002 (Box-folder 150: 8)
    - Lists of contacts, 1988 (Box-folder 150: 9)
    - Meetings file
      Agendas, correspondence, notes, papers, and transcripts of proceedings
      - Comité de liaison avec les États-Unis, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 150: 10)
      - General assemblies, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 151: 1)
      - Groupe Défense
        - 1992 (Box-folder 151: 2)
        - 1993 (Box-folder 151: 3-9)
      - Groupe Politique Étrangère, 1988 (Box-folder 151: 10)
      - Jury du concours international, 1990 (Box-folder 152: 1)
      - Jury du Prix Espoir, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 152: 2)
      - Memoranda and reports
        - 1987-1988 (Box-folder 152: 3)
        - 2001 (Box-folder 152: 4)
      - Papers and speeches, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 152: 5)
      - Printed matter
        - Brochures, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 152: 6)
        - Bulletin, 1998 (Box-folder 152: 7)
        - Clippings, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 152: 8)
        - Serial issues
          - 2000 (Box-folder 152: 9)
          - 2000-2001 (Box-folder 152: 10)
      - Statutes, undated (Box-folder 152: 11)
  - Fondation Singer-Polignac
    - Brochures
      - 1985-1998 (Box-folder 152: 12)
    - Correspondence
      - 1996-1999 (Box-folder 152: 13)
      - 2000-2001 (Box-folder 152: 14)
  - Institut Français des Relations Internationales (IFRI)
    - Correspondence, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 153: 1)
    - Meetings file, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 153: 2)
    - Printed matter